brainstorm3d.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Brainstorm Multimedia

**Company Data**

In compliance with reporting obligations stipulated in Article 10 of Law 34/2002 of July 11th, Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce in Spain, the Data Protection Law in Spain, and the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), Brainstorm Multimedia, SL (Brainstorm) as owner of the Brainstorm website, proceeds to communicate the identifying information required by that standard:

  * Company Name: BrainstormMultimedia, SL
  * Address: Avenida de la Albufera, 321, 3rd floor, Office 12.
  * VAT: B80767445
  * Email Address: [**webmaster@brainstorm3d.com**](mailto:webmaster@brainstorm3d.com)

The following information describes and regulates the Privacy Policy of the Brainstorm webpage that is published under the domain name www.brainstorm3d.com. Brainstorm may revise the Privacy Policy for its website at any time without notice. This latest revision is dated may 2018. The Terms of Use of this page can be found on the following link: [**Brainstorm website Terms of Use**](http://www.brainstorm3d.com/terms-conditions-use/).

Questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the “[ **Contact Us**](http://www.brainstorm3d.com/company/contact/)” link in the main menu. Or you can email us at: [**webmaster@brainstorm3d.com**](mailto:webmaster@brainstorm3d.com)

**Personal Data Protection**

Brainstorm is aware of the importance of the privacy of personal data and therefore has implemented a policy of data processing aimed at providing maximum security in the use and collection of the same, ensuring compliance with the regulations in force in the matter and configuring this policy as one of the basic pillars in the lines of action of the entity.

Brainstorm has implemented technical and organizational actions to prevent loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of personal data that could facilitate stakeholders as a result of access to the various sections of the Brainstorm website applying access measures security provided for in the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

**How we Collect and Use your Personal Data**

Brainstorm are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Therefore, Brainstorm will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where possible and appropriate, with the knowledge and consent of the individual concerned.

Also, while browsing through the web www.brainstorm3d.com you will find forms to contact Brainstorm which request personal data; when you fill in such contact forms, your data will enter our file system and will be used to fulfill your request. We will only use these data for marketing purposes in case you give us your consent.

The personal data might include your name, company, address, email, job title, phone number and product interest. Brainstorm will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified above us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

The data provided will form part of the relevant files depending on the specific and specific purpose that motivates the collection of them, essentially to maintain a commercial relationship and/or inform the users about Brainstorm product updates, new technologies and commercial activities such as trade shows. In this way, the particular information of each data processing will be provided next to each web form, being common to all of them the person in charge of the file: Brainstorm, domiciled in Avenida de la Albufera, 321, 3rd floor, 28031 Madrid, Spain, and the place and manner of exercise of rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition. In the event that you provided your data through an email, it will be part of a file whose purpose will be the management of your request, being applicable the rest of the above-mentioned premises.

Brainstorm will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

**Sharing Personal Data**

Brainstorm does not share personal data information with third parties for marketing purposes. Brainstorm can retrieve from or provide your data to our Distributors and Resellers, when required in order to better fulfill your sales or information request.

**Marketing**

We will not send you useless emails, we would just send communications to keep you informed about our activity, news and product updates, so we will send you such information if you consent to receive it. However, if you want to withdraw your consent to receive marketing information, this can be done by just clicking “unsubscribe” on the email communications you receive, or by sending us an email to **[marketing@brainstorm3d.com](mailto:marketing@brainstorm3d.com) **.

**Accesing, Modifying and Deleting your Information**

You have the right to access the data stored about you at any time. If you want to do so, please send an email to **[webmaster@brainstorm3d.com](mailto:webmaster@brainstorm3d.com)** and we will send you a copy of the information we have about you. We hold and process information only under your consent, so you have the right to access, modify or withdraw your data, please send an email to **[webmaster@brainstorm3d.com](mailto:webmaster@brainstorm3d.com) **and we will process your request.

**Cookies**

The site uses cookies that are stored on your computer. Cookies are small files that our computer sends to you, but they do not give us information about your name, or about any personal data of yours. The cookies we use cannot read data from your computer or read the cookies that exist on your computer.

When the user is browsing the Brainstorm webpage the server where it is hosted automatically recognizes the IP address of their computer, the day and time in which the visit, which leaves the visit begins, as well as information on the different sections. It is necessary that the server knows this data in order to be able to communicate and send the request made and through the browser can be seen on the screen.

If you wish you can configure your browser so that it will alert you on the screen if you are going to receive a cookie. The user can configure his computer so that he does not receive these cookies, this fact will not prevent that the information of the web site to be accessed.

**Hyperlinks**

The function of the Hyperlinks that appear in this Web is exclusively the one to inform to the user about the existence of other Web that contain information on the subject. Such hyperlinks are not suggestion or recommendation.

Brainstorm is not responsible for the contents of such linked pages, the operation or utility of Hyperlinks or the result of such links, nor does it guarantee the absence of viruses or other elements in them that may cause alterations in the computer system (hardware and software), documents or files of the user, excluding any liability for damages of any kind caused to the user for this reason.

* * *

Copyright © 2018 – Brainstorm Multimedia, SL – All rights reserved by copyright and international intellectual property laws and treaties. It is expressly prohibited to copy, reproduce or disseminate, in whole or in part, by any means.
